I'm always trying to figure out, like, where people are coming from so I can best meet them.
And when I see folks who are trusting in the government, I wonder where they're coming from.
I wonder if they maybe just have put certain things out of their mind or if they're just lying to themselves to feel good or to feel safe.
Because I'm sitting here watching Come Hell or High Water, which is the three-part documentary on Netflix about Katrina.
And I remember 2005.
And I remember watching the people of New Orleans be left behind.
I remember them being called refugees in their own country.
And the people of New Orleans remember being left behind.
And so I don't know why it is so hard to convince so many of you that what we have right here that's called a government, it ain't what we deserve as a people.
It may be what we have, but it's not what we deserve.
And I don't know what examples, and I don't know what more examples you need to know that.
But you're going to be given more shortly.
And I hope that there's a quick response in the way of waking up to us.
We'll see you next time.